<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Safe2Tell</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Section 1</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Section 2</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_example">Example action</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <color name="lrn_back">#FF4444</color>
    <color name="prob_back">#33B5E5</color>
    <color name="stor_back">#AA66CC</color>
    <color name="quiz_back">#99CC00</color>
    <color name="news_back">#FFBB33</color>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="description">Description of Event</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="submit_button">Submit</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Dumb text</string>

    <string name="about">Safe2Tell® provides YOUNG people a way to report any threatening behaviors or activities endangering themselves or someone they know, in a way that keeps them safe and anonymous.

Safe2Tell® is a 501c3 not-for-profit organization based on the Colorado Prevention Initiative for School Safety with initial funding from The Colorado Trust.

The program focuses on kids and the issues they face today.  This program was based on the Columbine Commission Report’s recommendation that students need a safe and anonymous way to keep lines of communication open.  They realized that tragedies could be prevented if young people had a way to tell someone what they knew without fearing retaliation.

The anonymity of all Safe2Tell reports is protected by C.R.S. 07-197.  This means the reporting party remains UNKNOWN by Colorado state law, signed by Governor Bill Ritter on May 3, 2007.



Now, using Safe2Tell®, they only have to make a call to make a difference.  By calling 1-877-542-7233 or submitting a tip through this web-site, young people can help anyone who is in trouble or prevent a tragedy.</string>

    <string-array name="drawerFields">
        <item>Stories</item>
        <item>About Us</item>
        <item>Learn</item>
        <item>Quiz</item>
        <item>Problems</item>
        <item>Tip</item>
        <item>Custom Card</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="problems">
        <item>Suicide</item>
        <item>Drug Abuse</item>
        <item>Domestic Violence</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="title_activity_submit__tip">New Tip</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="card1_title">New Safe2Tell App to be released soon!</string>
    <string name="card2_title">Did you know: One in every two students is a victim of Cyber-Bullying?</string>
    <string name="card3_title">Bullying stops in less than 10 seconds when a peer intervenes on the behalf of the victim!</string>
    <string name="card4_title">1 in 5 K-12 students is a victim of bullying!</string>
    <string name="card5_title">Help stop suicides, learn these life-saving tips!</string>



</resources>
